297份新婚贺礼
297 wedding gifts!
真是个小奇迹
It's a minor miracle.
总数居然在三百以下
Our final total is below 300.
好了  签完了
There. I am done.
五百本亲笔签名的《狂野斯道姆》
500 autographed copies of "Wild Storm."
我的婚礼前签名债还清了
My pre-wedding signing obligations are finished.
很好  签了这个
Good. Now sign this.
这又是什么
What's this one?
屋顶婚礼会场的最终款项
Final payment for the rooftop venue.
你是说那个完美的会场
You mean the perfect venue --
将曼哈顿美景尽收眼底
a 360-degree view of Manhattan,
星辰闪烁  世界就在我们脚下
the stars above us, the world at our feet.
贝克特不愿意从大楼一侧
It's too bad Beckett didn't want to bungee-jump
蹦极退场真是太可惜了
off the side of the building for our big exit.
那样多酷啊
Now, that would've been cool.
礼服明晚会到
The tuxes will be in tomorrow evening.
你跟埃斯波西托和莱恩说了吗
Did you tell Esposito and Ryan?
说了  他们会过来试穿并且带走礼服
I did. They will be here to try them on and to collect them.
你真是新郎可遇不可求的好伴郎
You are the most adorable best man a groom could hope for.
可能是门卫带上来更多贺礼了
Probably the concierge with more gifts.
杰拉德
Hi, Gerard.
放在那里  跟其它的放一块儿  谢谢
Put them over there - with the others. Thank you.
好了  我出门了
All right. I'm out.
-再见  -爸
- Bye. - Dad!
别忘了领结婚证要用的表格
Don't forget the forms for the marriage license!
这些就是我手上的案子了
Those are my case files.
有问题赶紧问  因为接下来的三周
Ask your questions, because I will be pretty much unreachable
-你们应该都联系不到我  -好吧
- for the next three weeks. - Okay.
哪个更让你激动  婚礼还是蜜月
What are you more excited about, the wedding or the honeymoon?
在马尔代夫的私人岛屿上玩三周
Three weeks in the Maldives on a private island?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
事实上  我不激动的只有一件事
Actually, the only thing I'm not excited about
就是在那么多人面前念结婚誓词
is having to say my vows in front of all those people.
没事的
Oh, you'll be fine.
就想象那些宾客是凶杀案疑犯
Just imagine your wedding guests are, uh, murder suspects.
只穿着内裤
In their underwear.
还是别了
Or not.
我结婚前超级紧张
You know, I was so nervous before my wedding
撞了墙  眼睛都淤青了
that I ran into a wall and got a black eye.
乱成一团很正常
You're supposed to be a wreck.
你将体验
You're about to experience
这辈子最重要的日子之一
one of the most important days of your life.
我真心为你高兴  探长
I'm so happy for you, detective.
伙计们
Hey, guys!
除了你要嫁的新郎官
In spite of who you're marrying.
谁准备好领结婚证了
So, who's ready to get her marriage license?
我  马上就好  我去拿包包
Me -- almost. I got to get my bag.
棒极了
Excellent.
阿丽克西斯要我提醒你们...
And Alexis wanted me to remind you --
她给我们打了电话  发了短信和电邮
She called, she texted, and she e-mailed.
我们会去的
We will be there.
还会带上黑色的皮鞋
And we'll bring our black shoes.
文件你都拿好了吧
Do you have our paperwork?
是的[我愿意]
I do.
就是练习一下  我...
I'm just practicing. I...
我拿好了
I do. I got it.
玩得开心
Have fun, guys.
再过72小时我们就结婚了
T-minus 72 hours until we are married.
感觉像在做梦
It feels like a dream.
那是因为我就是梦幻老公
That's 'cause I'm dreamy.
下一对
Next!
我们来了
Here we are.
理查德·卡塞尔先生和凯瑟琳·贝克特女士
Mr. Richard Castle and Ms. Katherine Beckett.
正是
That's us.
离婚证明
Proof of divorce?
是我的文件有什么问题吗
I-is there something wrong with my documents?
没问题
They're in order.
贝克特女士  你的呢
Ms. Beckett, do you have yours?
你说什么
Pardon me?
你的离婚证书
Your divorce paperwork.
不好意思  你们搞错了吧
I'm sorry. There's a mistake.
我没结过婚
I've --I've never been married.
根据记录  你结过
Well, according to this, you have.
看样子你还结着呢
And it looks like you still are.
我结婚了
I'm married?
跟谁
To whom?
罗根·奥拉里
Rogan O'Leary?!
罗根·奥拉里是哪位啊
Well, who is Rogan O'Leary?
她在斯坦福大学一年级时认识的男人
A guy she met - freshman year at Stanford.
我要吐了
Oh, I think I'm gonna be sick.
你嫁给他了
And you married him?
不算是
Not really.
就是的
Except she did.
他俩开车到拉斯维加斯  喝高了
The two of them drove to Cegas, had too much to drink,
觉得打车到
and thought it would be a riot
快速婚礼教堂结婚很酷炫
to take a cab to - a drive-through wedding chapel.
-不是吧  -是的
- You didn't. - She did.
是的  但我一直以为这是闹着玩的
Yeah, I did, but I never thought that it was for real.
几周后我就跟那男的分手了
And I broke up with the guy a couple weeks later
因为我发现他一再撒谎
after I found out he was a compulsive liar,
堕落腐化  还偷东西
degenerate, and a thief.
是的  但在这之前你已经嫁给他了
Yes, but not before you tied the knot.
我还以为你是一生只结一次婚的姑娘
And here I thought you were a one-and-done kind of girl.
你父亲知道这事吗
Does your father know about this?
我真要吐了
I really am gonna be sick.
是我的律师来了
And that'll be my lawyer.
你俩都满18岁了
You were both over 18.
不管当时是不是玩笑  或是本意如何
Regardless of your seriousness or intent at the time,
恐怕你们在"极速真爱"举行的婚礼
I'm afraid your wedding at the drive thru of love
是真实合法有效的
was real, legal, and binding.
我们三天后就要结婚了
Okay. We are getting married in three days.
恐怕结不成
I'm afraid you can't.
除非你先结束第一段婚姻
Not unless you terminate your first marriage.
我们请了三百名宾客  多数人是大老远飞来的
We have 300 people coming. Most of them are flying in.
我们要怎么跟他们说
So what are we gonna say to all of them?
亨利  有什么办法解决这件事吗
Henry, is there anything we can do to make this go away?
双方都同意离婚就可以
It's possible --if there's mutual consent.
我带了一份离婚协议来
I brought a dissolution-of-marriage contract,
我可以让法院加速审核  但是
and I could expedite it through the city, but...
你们得让奥拉里先生在上面签名
you'll have to get Mr. O'Leary to sign it, too.
怎么让他签  都过去15年了
How? It's been 15 years.
我完全不知道他现在在哪
I have no idea where he is.
好吧  我们好像找到他了
Okay, looks like we found him,
天哪  你丈夫还真厉害
but, man, is your husband a piece of work.
他不是我丈夫
He's not my husband!
法律上来说  他的确是
Except, legally, he is.
都有些什么资料
So, what do we know about him?
他四处游走
Well, your boy got around.
05年在奥斯丁被控偷窃
He was charged with theft in Austin in '05.
07年在爱荷华州因酒后驾车服过刑
He did time for a D.U.I. in Iowa in '07.
在肯塔基州因诈骗被捕
He was arrested for fraud in Kentucky, and --
这条好
This is a good one.
他在新奥尔良
He was put in jail
因为冒充联调局探员而被捕入狱
for impersonating an FBI agent in New Orleans.
鉴于他的斑斑劣迹  我得说
I must say, given his record,
你能这么多年对他不离不弃真不简单
I'm really surprised you stayed with him all these years.
你们知道他现在在哪吗
Do you know where he is now?
是的  他五年前好像在纽约州北部
Yeah, looks like he settled in a small town in Upstate New York
一个叫柳溪镇的地方定居了
called Willow Creek about five years ago.
有他的联系方式吗
Do you have his contact information?
现在就发给你
Texting right now.
罗根·奥拉里的
The voicemail for...
语音信箱
Rogan O'Leary.
已满  请稍后再试
...is full. Please try again later.
我找不到他
I'm not getting through.
要么电话响了一直不接
Either the phone rings incessantly
要么就转到已经满了的语音信箱
or I get - the "Voicemail is full" message.
那么  你想怎么样
So, what do you want to do?
我想结婚  你想怎么样
I want to get married. What do you want to do?
我也想结婚
I want to get married, too.
好啊  那就这么定了
Okay. Then it's settled.
你留在这儿  继续忙婚礼的事
You'll stay here - and keep the wedding on track.
那  你呢
And...you?
我去柳溪镇
I'm gonna go to Willow Creek.
我只有不到三天的时间找到罗根·奥拉里
I've got less than three days to find Rogan O'Leary
然后跟他离婚
and get a divorce.
他不值得你这么做
He's not worth it.
你说什么
Pardon me?
亲爱的  我和他做了五年邻居了
Sweetie, I've been his neighbor for five years.
他那张笑脸会让你乖乖地跟他上床
He's got a smile that will make your pants fall off.
但相信我  他是个麻烦精
But trust me -- he's trouble.
你知道在哪能找到他吗
Do you know where I can find him?
可别说我没警告过你
Don't say I didn't warn you.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我在找你们的一个酒保
I'm looking for one of your bartenders.
罗根·奥拉里
Rogan O'Leary?
别这样啊  蒂尔迪
Come on, Tildy!
算了
Never mind.
饶了我吧
Give me a break!
饶了你  我饶不死你
You want a break? I'll give you a break.
我干什么了
What the hell did I do?!
你干什么了  你什么没干
What did you do?! How about what didn't you do?!
我本以为你是来道歉的
I thought you came here to apologize,
告诉我你有多么愧疚
to tell me how sorry you are!
但不是  你竟然是来拿回你的东西的
But no! All you want is your stuff back?!
那根本就不是你的东西
It's not even your stuff!
是我们的东西
It's our stuff.
而且我需要那些东西才能把事情摆平
And I-I-I need it to make things right.
我受够了
I'm through!
滚出我的酒吧
Now, get out of my bar!
别闹了  宝贝
Come on, babe.
你不是来真的
You know you don't mean that.
你很爱我的
You love me too much.
爱得够深吧
How's that for love?
小凯
Kit Kat?
是你吗
Is that you?
你好啊  罗根
Hello, Rogan.
看来  你还是没怎么变
So, I see you haven't changed.
什么  那事啊
What? That?
没有啦
Nah.
那只是...
Come on, that was just a, uh...
俗话说的  情侣闹个小矛盾
that was just a lovers' quarrel, as they say.
那个
So...
小凯  你怎么来柳溪镇了
so, Kit Kat, what brings you to Willow Creek?
你走在怀旧的小路上
You walking the nostalgia trail?
寻找旧情人  想要发现真正的自己
Tracking down old flames to discover who you really are?
不是
No.
还记得咱俩曾经去过拉斯维加斯吗
Do you remember a trip that we took to Vegas?
有点记不清了
I don't know. It's a little fuzzy.
不过  我最好的回忆大都是模糊的
But, uh, most of my best memories are.
那你还记不记得  当时我们
So, when we were there, do you recall
叫了一辆出租车  去了教堂
a cab ride and a drive-up chapel?
忘了  但我记得
Nope, but I do recall
我们在一家脱衣舞店吃了霸王餐
a dine-and-dash on the strip.
还记得吗  吃的大三明治
Do you remember... with the hoagies?
在收银台时  "你们俩  滚出去"
At the counter... "Hey, you! Get out of there!"
你可能觉得这挺好玩的
Well, you know what, you're probably gonna find this funny,
但是  实际上
but, as it turns out,
你和我已经
you and I have been...
结婚  15年了
married for...15 years.
结婚
Married?
真的吗
For realsies?
是的
Yeah.
太搞笑了
That is hilarious!
什么  你知道这事多久了
What... how long have you known that?
刚刚才知道
I just found out.
不过  也不是什么大事
But you know what, it's not a big deal,
因为你需要做的只是
Because all you have to do is...
签了这个
sign this...
然后你就恢复自由了
and you're off the hook.
好  好  好
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
好
Yeah.
不过  这个
But, you know, it's...
这种不自由也挺好的
it is a pretty nice hook, you know?
见鬼  咱俩都结婚这么久了
I mean, heck, we have been married this long.
或许我们可以再给彼此一次机会
Maybe we should just give it a chance...
不吗  好吧
No. I know, I know.
这么说  让我签这些表格
So... it must be pretty important to you
对你来说肯定很重要了
to have me sign these forms, then?
你大老远的从...
You know, if you've driven all the way from...?
纽约过来
New York.
纽约
我猜猜  你是律师
Let me guess... lawyer?
探长
Detective.
Detective!
是的  纽约警局
Yeah. NYPD.
快说说  一个曾经撬过
So, tell me, how does a girl go
珍珠果酱乐队的巡演大巴车锁
from picking the lock on Pearl Jam's tour bus
偷埃迪·维德[主唱]的牛仔夹克的女孩
so she can steal Eddie Vedder's jean jacket
怎么成了警察了
to becoming a cop?
我...
I...
我很抱歉
You know, I'm sorry.
你肯定很忙  我应该走了
I...I... you're obviously busy, and I should probably just go.
但麻烦你签了这个
But if you could just sign this...
好的  当然
No. Yeah. Of course.
我很愿意
I'd... I would... I would really love to sign
-签这份离婚协议  -很好
- this dissolution-of-marriage agreement for you. - Great.
不过  你得先帮我做件事
But...you're gonna have to do something for me first.
好了
Okay.
要那一条
Which one?
朴素点的  也就是这条
The easy one, which is this one.
谢谢
Thank you.
贝克特有消息了吗
Any news from Beckett?
几个小时前她给我发了短信
Uh, she texted me a couple hours ago --
说她找到了  之后就没消息了
Said she'd found him, but I haven't heard from her since.
可能他们在叙旧
Maybe they're catching up.
是啊  他们有挺多共同点的
Sure. No, sure. They got a lot in common.
她可以聊聊那些被她送进监狱的人
She can talk about all the people she's put in prison,
他可以聊聊那些他在监狱遇到的人
And he can talk about all the people he's met in prison.
阿丽克西斯  我还没发福到这个程度
Um, Alexis, I haven't gained this much daddy weight.
不可能
That can't be right.
我检查尺寸检查了十遍
I double-checked the size 10 times.
也许是你终于
Hey, maybe you finally hit
等到了你的生长周期  兄弟
that growth spurt you've been waiting on, bro.
她来电话了
And that's her.
还好吗
Hey. What's up?
我遇到了点小麻烦
Okay, so, there has been a little glitch.
-他不愿意签字吗  -不是  他愿意
- He won't sign? - Oh, no. He'll sign,
但是他让我先替他做件事
But he wants me to do something first.
什么样的事
What kind of thing?
他让我从他前女友的卡车里
He wants me to break into his ex-girlfriend's truck
帮他偷一个车库开门器
and steal a garage-door opener.
好吧  为什么呢
O...kay. Why?
看来  他们俩分手后
Apparently, after they broke up,
他前女友拿走了他的一些东西
his ex-girlfriend took a few of his things,
他想要回来
and he wants them back.
他需要拿车库钥匙进他女友家吗
And he needs the garage-door opener to get into her place?
是她妈妈的家  但是也对
Her...mom's place, but yeah.
鉴于他的种种案底  他怎么不自己去偷
But given his record, why doesn't he just steal it himself?
因为她的卡车就停在她酒吧的外面
Because her truck is parked right outside of her bar,
他靠近不了
and he can't get close to it
因为有人看见他就会告诉他前女友
without someone spotting him and then telling her.
你真的要这么做
And you're actually thinking about doing this?
如果我不干  他就不会签字
If I don't, he won't sign.
卡塞尔  他可以拖上好几年
Castle, he could drag this on for years.
要是你被抓到怎么办
And if you get caught?
不会的
I won't.
听着卡塞尔  我只有乖乖听他的
Look, Castle, he's got me over a barrel here.
如果我不做  我们就结不了婚
If I don't do this, we don't get married.
赶紧弄完就回家吧
Just get this over with and come home.
事情办好我就给你打电话
I'll call you when I'm done.
完成任务
Mission accomplished.
你拿到车库的遥控了
So, you got the remote?
是的  没有被抓住
Yes. And I wasn't caught.
你确定他现在就会签字了吗
And you're sure he'll sign the papers now?
他肯定会签的
Oh, he's gonna sign them, all right.
我不会让他说不的
I'm not taking "No" for an answer.
告诉大家婚礼如期举行
Tell everyone that this wedding is on.
我很快就会回来的
I'll be on my way back to the city soon.
-我等不及了  -再见
- Can't wait. - Bye.
给我回来  罗根
Get back here, Rogan!
-够了  伙计  够了  -罗根
- All right, man! All right! - Rogan!
停下
Stop!
有没有搞错
Really?!
你看到车牌了吗
Did you get the license of the truck?
那车没有车牌
It didn't have one.
但是那两个人都带着面具
But both of the men were wearing masks.
你的朋友被他们带走了  他叫什么
And your friend who got taken -- what's his name?
罗根  罗根·奥拉里
Rogan -- Rogan O'Leary.
什么  你为什么合上笔记本
What -- why are you closing your notebook?
女士  我们部门没有闲暇
Ma'am, our department doesn't have the resources
调查奥拉里先生的每件案子
to investigate every claim involving Mr. O'Leary.
可有人把他带走了
But someone took him.
是啊
I'm sure they did.
而且他们肯定有充分理由这么做
I'm sure they had a very good reason.
过了几天
And in a few days,
他就会出现  喝得烂醉  满身淤青  痛苦不堪
he'll show up drunk, bruised, and sorry as hell.
我等不了那么多天  我现在就得找到他
I don't have a few days. I need to find him now.
女士  作为女人跟你说句心里话
Ma'am, from one woman to another...
放手吧
Let him go.
他被绑架了  怎么会  可是
He's been abducted?! H-how -- but --
-是啊  我也不敢相信  -好吧
- I know. I don't believe it, either. - O-okay.
我讨厌这样  但我们是不是该推迟一下
I hate to ask, but do you think maybe we should postpone?
不  我不会放弃的  我要找到他
No. No, I'm not giving up. I'm gonna find him.
-怎么找  -我可是个警探
- How? - Well, I'm a detective.
肯定有人知道一些情况
Someone here has to know something.
你不该一个人去做  我马上赶过来
You shouldn't be doing this alone. I'm coming up there.
-真的吗  -是的
- Are you sure? - Yes.
当然  这里的一切都布置好了
Absolutely. E-everything here is completely under control.
几小时后见
I-I will see you in a few hours.
再见
Bye.
你好
Hello?
我是理查德·卡塞尔
Yes, this is Richard Castle.
什么
What?
婚礼会场不能用了
We lost our venue?
怎么可能呢
How is that even possible?!
他们今晚办了个马戏团聚会
They had a circus party there tonight
有人表演了喷火的把戏
with some first-time fire breathers.
现在我们的顶楼宴会厅没有台子了
Now our rooftop venue does not have a floor.
这就是一场灾难
This is a disaster.
结婚的地方没了  结婚的对象也不在
No place to get married and no one to get married to.
这都不是灾难二字就可以描述的
I think "Disaster" is an understatement.
所谓的灾难其实就是隐藏的机遇
So-called "Disaster" is merely opportunity in disguise.
我们重新找一个地方举办婚礼就行了
We'll just find another place to hold the wedding.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
在曼哈顿我们两天之内
Where are we gonna find a venue in Manhattan
上哪去找一个能容下300人的宴会厅
that holds 300 people -- in less than two days?
我们已经有个地方了
Ooh! We already have one.
不在曼哈顿
Not in Manhattan.
我们可以在汉普斯顿的房子举办婚礼
We can move the whole party to our house in the Hamptons.
对呀
Yes.
Yes!
我们在那儿办过更大的聚会呢
We've held larger parties than this out there.
我们可以租豪车接客人过去
We rent luxury buses to shuttle our guests
给婚庆公司报销车费
and pay the vendors' transportation costs.
太聪明了
Brilliant!
早上我会第一时间给管家打电话
I will call the housekeeper first thing in the morning
让他们把地方准备好
and have them start getting the place ready.
你确定这样行得通
You really think we can pull this off?
拜托
Oh, please!
我们公司没有地方的时候
I once staged "A chorus line" on a subway platform
我还在地铁站台拍演了《平步青云》
when our company lost its space.
我觉得我可以办得到
I think I can move a wedding.
阿丽克西斯会帮忙的
Alexis will help with everything.
你只要保证
You just make sure
凯瑟琳找到她那个游手好闲的丈夫
Katherine finds - that deadbeat husband of hers.
好了
Yes.
谢谢你能赶过来  宝贝
Thanks for coming up, babe.
真抱歉这场乌龙
I'm so sorry about this whole mess.
未婚夫不就是应该帮助
Oh, what's a fiance for, if not to help find
未婚妻找到现任丈夫的嘛
his future wife's current husband?
况且没有我的干扰  阿丽克西斯和我妈
And Alexis and mother will get far more done
会更有效率
without my interference.
我只希望她们不是徒劳
Well, I just hope that all their work is not for nothing.
你觉得罗根的前女友能帮我们找到他
You think Rogan's ex will be able to help us find him?
他们曾经同居
They lived together.
如果我们走运的话  她可能知道
If we're lucky, she'll be able to tell us
他惹上了什么麻烦
what kind of mess he was mixed up in.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
你好  女士
Uh, hi, ma'am.
纽约警察  我们在找罗根·奥拉里
NYPD. We're looking for Rogan O'Leary.
你们要是找到他就别让他回来了
Well, if you find him, you can keep him.
老妈  别说了
Stop it, mama.
昨天在酒吧看到你了
You were in the bar yesterday.
对  我是想找奥拉里先生帮忙
Yeah, I was hoping - that Mr. O'Leary could help us
破一件陈年旧案
with...an old case,
但他昨晚好像被绑架了
but it seems that he was abducted last night.
有谁会绑架他
By who?
我们希望你能提供点线索
We were hoping you could tell us.
可不是我  要我直接杀了他
Wasn't me. I'd have offed him.
老妈  够了
Mama, that's enough.
他是被两个男人拖上一辆生锈的皮卡带走的
Look, he was taken by two men in a rusty pickup truck.
你知道他们是谁吗
Do you have any idea who they were?
不知道
No.
但他总是用各种方式惹恼别人
But he's always working crazy angles, pissing people off.
你是因为这个和他分手的吗
Is that why you left him?
不
No.
这我都习惯了
I was used to that.
他从我这拿了钱要筹划些什么
But he took money from me for one of his schemes --
说会让我们暴富
said he was gonna make us rich.
当然钱都打水漂了  我可能连酒吧都保不住
He lost it all, of course. Now I might lose the bar.
但即便他劣迹斑斑
Thing is, in spite of it all...
我还是爱他
I love him.
我可以忽视
I mean, I can overlook the fact that --
他没有正规工作
That he's not - a "Regular job" Kind of guy
或者他因为昏迷的妻子而不能和我结婚
or that he can't marry me while his wife's in a coma,
但他不该危及我的酒吧
but he should never have put my bar in jeopardy.
抱歉  他说他有个妻子
I'm sorry -- - he said that he had a wife?
昏迷的妻子
A wife in a coma?
对  他俩在学校时候结的婚  她出了事故
Yeah. He married in college. She got in an accident.
昏迷15年了
Been in a coma 15 years.
好像叫"凯蒂"什么的
"Katie"...Something.
挺凄惨的
It's kind of tragic, really.
确实非常凄惨
So very tragic.
他昨天提到什么麻烦了吗
Did he mention any trouble yesterday?
或者有没有说他非常需要
Or say anything about you having something in your possession
你的什么东西
that he urgently needed?
车库或房子里的什么东西
Something in the garage or house?
对  想起来了
Actually, yeah.
他说想要我从他公寓拿的那台笔记本电脑
He said he needed the laptop I took from his apartment.
还说马上就要
Said he needed it right away.
他说为什么了吗
Did he say why?
没有  但那是我的电脑
No, but since it's my laptop,
我估计他是胡扯
I figured it was a line of bull,
只是想让我把电脑给他
that he wanted me to give it up
然后他好卖了换钱罢了
so he could sell it for the money.
他这么着急想要拿到电脑
Given how anxious he was to get his hands on it,
这可能和他被绑架有关
it might have something to do with his abduction.
蒂尔迪  我们能借用一下这台电脑吗
Tildy, could we borrow that laptop?
或许能帮我们找到他
Might help us find him.
我们是破案专家
We are trained professionals,
罗根可能惹上了大麻烦
and Rogan might be in some very, very serious trouble.
他确实有麻烦了
He's in trouble, all right.
这么多年  他一直知道我们结了婚
I mean, all these years, he knew that we were married.
我来的时候他就知道
He knew when I got here.
而15年来
And for 15 years,
他居然一直用这个借口来逃避婚姻
he's been using that as an excuse not to commit.
昏迷中的妻子
Coma wife...
很有才嘛
it's kind of brilliant.
你是说"卑鄙"吧
You mean "Despicable," Right?
对  我...就是这个意思
Yeah. That's...what I meant.
你在电脑上发现什么了吗
Did you find anything on the laptop?
他们的往来邮件都相当色情
Their e-mails to each other are fairly pornographic,
但这都不是被绑架的原因
but nothing - that would get a man abducted.
也许我们该打电话给托瑞
You know what -- maybe we should call Tory
让她远程访问  看看我们有没有漏掉什么
and have her access it remotely, see if we're missing anything.
我们应该再去罗根的公寓
And we should re-check Rogan's apartment --
查查有没有线索
see if there's anything there
能让我们知道他惹了什么麻烦
that could tell us what he was involved with.
我得给蕾妮打个电话
I got to call Lanie.
今天下午赶不及参加我的单身温泉派对了
I'm not gonna make my spa bachelorette party this afternoon.
你的单身派对也有裸女吗
You were gonna have naked ladies at your party, too?
亲爱的  做好你手头的事
Do what you need to do, girl.
汉普顿计划正全面展开
Operation Hamptons is in full swing,
等你度蜜月回来的时候
And we'll have a newlyweds spa day
我们就举办个新婚夫妇温泉节
when you get back from your honeymoon.
蕾妮  我也不知道什么时候能回来
Yeah, lanie, look, I don't know when we're gonna get back,
你能去我家拿一下我的礼服
so can you go to my place, pick up the dress,
帮我保管一晚吗
and take it up with you tonight?
它会静静地等你的
It will be there waiting for you.
谢啦  蕾妮
Okay, thanks, lane.
希望我们能回得去
Assuming we get there at all.
我们不改变计划是不是太不理智
Are we crazy - for going ahead with this?
确实  但我们别无选择
Yes. But what other choice do we have?
听着  我不想
Look, I don't want to
在几个月以后再来补办婚礼
have a makeup wedding in a few months, okay?
我想立刻结婚
I want to do this now.
我们赶快找到你丈夫  好明天顺利结婚
So let's find this husband of yours and get married tomorrow.
再说  事情也不能再糟了
Besides, not like - things can get any crazier.
瞧瞧这是谁来了
Well. What do we have here?
我言之过早了
I spoke too soon.
罗根在哪里
Where's Rogan?
大家放松一点  把枪放下
Okay, let's just relax and put down the guns
别让人受伤...
so no one gets hu--
卡塞尔
Castle?!
如果你不告诉我罗根在哪的话
See, the only ones getting hurt are gonna be you
唯一受伤的只会是你自己
if you don't tell me where Rogan's at.
我没事
I'm fine.
我们不知道他在哪
We don't know where he is.
我们跟他都不怎么熟
We barely know who he is.
那你们来他公寓干嘛
Then what are you doing in his place?!
和你一样  来找他
Looking for him -- same as you.
这是什么
What's this?
这是你吗
Is that you?
那就是了
That's a yes.
这样的话  你和罗根是夫妻
Okay, well, according to this, you and Rogan are married.
不是说不认识他吗
Thought you didn't know the guy!
这可是个滑稽的故事
Okay, well, funny story there.
假如我让你流血你还会觉得好笑吗
Is it still gonna be funny when I make you bleed?
不会
No.
你老公欠我一大笔钱
Your husband owes me a lot of money.
-说  他在哪  -我不知道
- Now, where is he? - I don't know.
好吧  既然你是他的老婆
All right, well, seeing as how you're his wife,
你可以替他还钱
you can pay me.
他究竟欠你多少钱
Exactly how much does he owe you?
扣掉订金  还差5000块服务费
Less his down payment, $5,000 for services rendered.
今天到期
Payable today.
什么服务
What kind of services?
这是我和他之间的事情
That's between me and him.
如果你想让我还钱
If you want me to pay you,
我得知道我的钱花在了哪里
then tell me what I'm paying for.
好吧  也算合理
All right. Well, that seems fair.
上礼拜你老公雇我们偷一部手机
Your husband hired us to steal a phone last week.
谁的手机
Whose phone?
一个叫塞弗丽的女孩
Some girl named Sapphire.
路边旅馆的一个脱衣舞女
Some stripper down at the roadhouse.
5000块就为了一部脱衣舞女的手机
$5,000 for a stripper's phone?
手机里有什么
What was on it?
我不知道  没问  也不关心
I don't know. Didn't ask, don't care.
我只想拿回我的钱
I just want my money!
我们会帮你要回来的
And we'll get it to you.
但我们得先找到罗根
We just need to find Rogan first.
不  奥拉里太太
No, Mrs. O'Leary.
我现在就要我的钱
I want my money now.
卡塞尔  你该不会正好有...
Um, Castle, you wouldn't happen...
大部分现金被我妈拿走了
Uh, well, my mother took most of my cash,
阿丽克西斯拿走了我的银行卡
and Alexis has my ATM card.
我想你应该不收支票吧
I don't suppose you'd take a check.
那  我  我有
That's -- uh, uh, no, I got -- I got --
我有500块
I have $500 right here.
多给我们点时间
Ju-just for more time.
剩下的钱我们到时候还
We'll owe you the rest of the 5 grand.
我们还需要一点时间
We just need a little bit more time.
再给你们12小时
You bought yourself 12 hours.
如果我回来的时候你们凑不齐钱
If you don't have the full amount when I come back,
我就打断你们的腿
I start breaking legs.
明白了吗
Do you understand?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
不  奥拉里太太  我不好
No, Mrs. O'leary, I'm not okay.
我很喜欢我的腿  还有你的
I happen to like my legs -- and yours, too.
为什么你老公要花5000块让摩托手
And why is your husband paying bikers over 5 grand
偷一部脱衣舞女的手机
for a stripper's phone?
首先  能别叫他我老公吗
First of all, can we please stop calling him my husband?
其次  我不知道  不过我猜
And secondly, I don't know, but I'm guessing
这一定和绑架有关
it has something to do with the abduction.
喂  我是贝克特
Hey. It's Beckett.
我要你们帮我远程搜查一台笔记本
Yeah, I need you guys to set up remote access to scrub a laptop.
卡塞尔  你能查一下那个旅馆的地址吗
Castle, can you look up the address to the roadhouse?
我想知道脱衣舞女的手机上究竟有什么
I want to know what was on that stripper's phone.
找一家本地脱衣舞酒吧
Find a local strip bar?
这个我擅长
Now, that, I know how to do.
我不知道你们在说什么
Look, I don't know what you're talking about.
没人偷我的手机
No one stole my phone.
你确定
Are you sure?
是的  就在这儿
Yeah. It's right here.
看到没
See?
手机里会不会有什么别人想要的东西
Is there anything on it that anyone might want?
就是部手机而已
It's just a phone.
到底是怎么回事
What is this all about?
你认识一个叫罗根·奥拉里的人吗
Do you know a guy named Rogan O'Leary?
无可奉告  非常抱歉
Can't help you. Sorry.
等等  塞弗丽  求你了
Wait, Sapphire, please.
他现在可能有大麻烦
He may be in real trouble,
假如你知道什么可以让我们找到他...
so if you know something that can help us find him...
如果你们不是来看跳舞的
Look, if you don't want a dance,
那就失陪了
then I need to move on.
她一定知道什么
She knows something.
不论是什么  她不想告诉我们
Well, whatever it is, she doesn't want to tell us.
我在这也没有权力让她说
And I don't have - the jurisdiction to make her.
凯特  是我
Kate, it's -- it's me.
蕾妮
Lanie?
什么事
What's wrong?
我刚去你公寓拿你的婚纱
I went to your apartment to pick up your dress,
可是...
and...
可是什么
And what?
凯特
Kate, a-a-a...
楼上公寓的一个水管破了
A pipe burst - in the apartment above, and...
天呐
Oh, no.
不  别告诉我
No. Don't tell me.
我尽力了  亲爱的
I tried, sweetie.
我想尽了一切办法
I-I did everything that I could,
可婚纱已经被毁得不像样了
but there was just too much damage.
凯特
Kate...
那个婚纱
The dress,
没法再穿了
it's gone!
一件婚纱而已  又不是世界末日
It's only a dress. It's not the end of the world.
我怎么觉得就是呢
Then why does it feel like it is?
我们的婚礼应该如童话一般
Our wedding was supposed to be magical.
应该是我俩最完美的一天
It was supposed to be our perfect day.
可现在却...
And now it's just...
支离破碎
falling apart.
那我们就一起把它拼凑起来
So we'll put it back together.
卡塞尔  我现在还是别人的妻子
Castle, I'm married to someone else.
我还不知道那个人在哪里
And I have no idea where he is.
我们一点线索也没有
We don't have any leads.
雪上加霜的先是会场  现在又来这个
And to make things worse, the venue, and then now this?
感觉这就像是一个强烈的征兆
I mean, it just feels like all of this is one big sign.
也许这就是一个征兆
Well, maybe it is a sign.
预示着我们爱情  是伟大的
A sign that ours is a great love story.
毕竟哪个伟大的爱情故事
'Cause what's a great love story
不是经历了重重阻挠呢
without obstacles to overcome?
每个童话故事里都有
Every fairy tale has them,
唯有真爱才能穿过种种阻碍
terrible trials that only the worthy can transcend.
但你不能放弃
But you can't give up.
事情就是如此
That's the deal.
如果我们想要幸福美满  就不能放弃
We want the happy ending, we can't give up.
这就是我要嫁给你的原因
And that's why I want to marry you.
我是托瑞
Hey, it's Tory.
我想我找到了线索
I think I may have found something.
我搜查了那台笔记本
I was scrubbing the laptop
结果找到了一个隐藏文件夹
and came across a hidden folder.
里面有什么
What's in it?
照片
Pictures.
从照片属性来看
According to image data,
它们是最近从某人的手机里下载下来的
they were recently downloaded from someone's phone.
大部分都无关紧要  不过其中有几张
Most of them are innocuous, but there are a couple of them
我觉得你有必要看一下
that, um... I think you need to see.
我给你发过去了
I'm e-mailing them now.
怎么了
What?
我想我知道你鬼鬼祟祟的老公为什么
I think I know why - your scheming, scamming husband
想偷这个脱衣舞女的手机了
wanted to steal that stripper's phone.
仔细看看
Check it out.
就是一男的看脱衣舞  有什么了不得的
It's a guy with a stripper. What's the big deal?
有什么了不得的
What's the big deal?
十分了不得
That is the big deal.
这是当地的牧师
It's the local pastor.
能让你老公花大钱换照片的原因
There's only one reason your husband would pay that much
只有一个
to get these photos.
他在敲诈上帝的仆人
He was blackmailing a man of God.
一位乐享淫欲的牧师
A pastor with skin in the game.
他有充分的动机想让罗根消失
And motive to make Rogan disappear.
谢谢您能见我们  牧师
Thank you for meeting with us, pastor.
你在电话里说事出紧急
Well, you said on the phone it was urgent,
而救人于危急是我的使命
and helping people is my calling.
那你的使命也包括帮助那些坐在你腿上
Does that include helping people out of their clothes
尽情展示胴体的人吗
while they're sitting on your lap?
你从哪搞到的
Where did you get those?
我看你非常清楚照片是哪来的
I think you already know the answer to that.
看来你们也是图财的了
I suppose you want money, too.
我是个牧师  不是取款机
I am a pastor, not a bank!
我们不是来讹你的
We're not here to blackmail you.
不是吗
You're not?
事情始于六个月前
It started six months ago.
我当时...
I had...
一时糊涂
a moment of weakness.
被那舞女拍了个现行
That stripper got photos of me.
从此我就没安生日子过了
It's been a nightmare ever since.
今天要一千  明天要五百
$1,000 here, $500 there.
也就是说讹你的是塞弗丽  不是罗根
So, Sapphire was blackmailing you, not Rogan?
一开始他没有  但后来罗根肯定发现了
At first. Then Rogan must've found out.
他不知用什么办法搞到了照片
He got his hands on the photos somehow.
他说如果我给他两万五
He said if I gave him $25,000,
他就能彻底解决掉这些照片
he would make them disappear forever.
如果我不给钱
And if I didn't,
他就把这些照片寄给本地教会
he would release them to the Willow Creek register.
所以为了弄回这些照片  你才绑架了他
So, is that why you kidnapped him? To get those photos back?
什么
What?!
我才没有绑架他
I didn't kidnap him!
你们把我看成什么人了
What kind of a man do you think I am?!
从照片上就能看出你是什么人
Well, I think we have a pretty good picture.
而且不止一张
We have a few pictures, actually.
我都打算付钱了
No, I was going to pay him.
我发誓  不信来看
I swear. Look.
本来今天早上我准备把钱给他
I was supposed to meet him here this morning with the money.
然后他把那笔记本和照片交给我
He was going to hand over the laptop and the photos,
但他一直没来
but he never showed.
马上就来  门罗太太
Be right with you, Mrs. Monroe.
所以你也不知道罗根在哪  是谁绑了他
So, you have no idea where Rogan is or who might've taken him?
不知道
No.
但如果你们找着他  告诉他钱已经备好了
But if you find him, tell him I am ready to pay.
我只希望这破事早点了结
I just want this to end.
让您久等了  门罗太太
Thank you for waiting, Mrs. Monroe.
那么你老公截了别人的发财路
So, your husband is hijacking someone else's blackmail?
还挺聪明  也很邪恶
Kind of ingenious, in a... degenerate sort of way.
塞弗丽肯定不这么想
Not if you're Sapphire.
如果你是塞弗丽
If you're Sapphire,
来钱门道被人堵了肯定恼火
you're pissed that you lost your income stream,
会想把这些照片夺回来
and you want those photos back.
抱歉  塞弗丽走了
I'm sorry, but Sapphire's gone.
你们俩刚问完话  她就逃了
She bolted right after she talked to you guys.
臭娘们害得我替她当班
Bitch stuck me with her shift.
你知道能在哪找到她吗
Do you know where we could find her?
你可以去他男朋友那找找
You could try her boyfriend's place.
他们算是在同居
They sort of live together.
他名叫吉米·拉兹
His name's Jimmy Lutz.
他在183号公路边上有座农场
He's got a farm off route 183.
我们真该给她小费
We really should tip.
就是这里
There it is.
就是那辆卡车
That's the truck.
把罗根劫走的那辆
The one that took Rogan.
你看
Here.
看看谷仓那边
Check out the barn.
看来我们找到劫匪了
Looks like we found our kidnappers.
我们报警吧
Then we should call the police.
-理由是什么  -他们手里有枪
- And tell them what? - That they have guns.
在他们自己的地盘上持枪  受宪法保护
On their own property, which is their constitutional right.
我们没法证明他们劫了罗根
We don't have proof that they have Rogan.
暂时没法
Yet.
暂时  什么暂时
"Yet"? What do you mean, "yet"?
来吧  卡塞尔
Come on, Castle.
我们进去看看他是不是被关在那里
Let's see if that's where they're keeping him.
你明天还想不想结婚了
Do you want to get married tomorrow or not?
万一被他们抓住了呢
What if we get caught?
就说我们是城里出来玩的
We tell them we're tourists from the city.
走迷路了
We got lost.
是啊  这法子在电影里可管用了
Yes. That worked out really well in "Deliverance."
就先从那谷仓找起吧
Okay, let's start with that barn.
这地方就跟乡村恐怖片的开头似的
Place looks like the start of an Amish horror film.
卡塞尔
Castle.
罗根
Rogan?
是你吗
Is that you?
吓我一大跳
I was not expecting that.
罗根
Rogan!
笑死我了
oh, my God.
笑死我了  老兄  你真该听听你那动静
Oh, my God. Dude, you should've heard yourself.
不要  啊啊啊
"Oh! Aah!"
小凯  这人谁啊
Kit Kat, who is this guy?
小凯
"Kit Kat"?
他是理查德·卡塞尔  我的未婚夫
This guy is Richard Castle, my future husband.
是吗
Really?
就冲刚才那小甜嗓
Well, after his little scream,
你最好检查下他的家伙事
you may want to, uh, re-check his man parts.
我的家伙事粗着呢  劳你关心了
My man parts are just fine, thank you very much.
咱们能不能别讨论什么家伙事了
Could everyone please stop saying "man parts"?
你们怎么找到我的
So, how did you find me?
简单  我们只要
Well, we just followed the trail
一路闻着堕落和欺诈的臭气
of disappointment and deception,
就直接找到你了
led us right to you.
厉害啊  你跟个混蛋订婚了
Oh, wow. You're engaged to a douche.
快给我解开绳子  咱们赶紧逃走
Here, why don't you untie me so we can get out of here?
好
Fine.
你才是混蛋
You're a douche.
好了
There.
你怎么不接着解了
W-what are you -- what are you doing?
解开一只手就够了
Freeing up one hand.
签个字又不用两只手
That's all you need to sign this.
说得好  小凯
Good one, Kit Kat.
这笑话好笑
That's hilarious.
我没跟你开玩笑
I'm not joking.
你要是想脱身逃走  那就得先签字
If you want me to cut you loose, then sign the papers.
你先让我逃出去  我再签字
I'll sign the papers when we're out of here.
现在就签
Sign them now.
什么  你不相信我吗
What? You don't trust me?
你毕竟敲诈了一位牧师
In fairness, you did blackmail a pastor.
等等  就等一下
Wait, wait, wait. Just hold on.
你就不想听听我的说法吗
Don't you want to hear my side of it?
我不在乎
I don't care about your side!
我只要你把这文件签了
I just want you to sign these papers.
我想我们还是先等安全了
You know, maybe we should wait to do this
再来签字吧
till we get somewhere safe.
就是  听那家伙事的话
Yes. Listen to man parts.
我们先离开这鬼地方
Let's get the hell out of here.
你好再次玩失踪吗
So you can disappear again?
再被绑架吗  没门
Or get kidnapped? No.
现在就在虚线上把名字签了
Just sign these papers right now on the dotted line.
你不懂
You don't understand.
这些家伙要杀了我
Those guys are gonna kill me.
就为了几张敲诈的照片
Over blackmail photos?
他们不会杀了你的  罗根
They're not gonna kill you, Rogan.
话说回来  这样一来我们的麻烦就解决了
Though, if you think about it, that would solve our problem.
听着  这不仅仅是关于牧师的事
Listen, this isn't about the pastor, okay?
那脱衣舞女的手机里还有其他照片
T-there were other photos on t-that stripper's phone --
那些照片和她男朋友有关
photos that had something to do with her boyfriend.
吉米·拉兹
Jimmy Lutz?
是的  但我觉得这不是他真名
Yeah, but I-I don't think that's his real name.
我的意思是  那对丑兄弟
I mean, t-the ugly brothers --
他们一直叫他别的名字
they -- they always, uh, called him something else,
好像是什么巴保兹
like... Barbozza something.
等等  叫巴保兹
Wait -- Barbozza?
没错
Yeah.
米奇·巴保兹吗
You mean, like Mickey Barbozza?
对  对  就是这名字
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
他很想要那些照片
I mean, this guy wants - those pictures something fierce,
但我没告诉他照片在哪
but I wouldn't tell him where they are
因为我不想把蒂尔迪扯进来
'cause I didn't want him going after Tildy.
打断下  我们是在说米奇·巴保兹
I-I'm sorry -- are we talking about Mickey Barbozza,
那位消失许久的黑帮杀手吗
the mob hit man who disappeared about a decade --
没错  没错  就是这人  就是他
Oh, yes. Yeah, that's him. That's the guy.
卡塞尔  帮我解开他  我们得离开这
Castle, help me untie him. We got to get out of here.
等等  等等  那人到底有多凶
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. So, h-how bad is this guy?
他为了躲避搜捕杀了六个人
He eluded a massive manhunt by killing half a dozen people,
联调局就一直在通缉他
and the FBI's been - looking for him ever since.
那  他一直躲在这里吗
And, so, wh-- he's been hiding out up here?
没错  恭喜你  罗根
Yeah. Congratulations, Rogan.
你碰巧偷了一位潜逃黑帮成员的照片
You accidentally stole photos of a fugitive mobster.
好吧  但这不是我本意
Okay, but that was not my intent.
快点  我们走
Come on. Let's go.
只有我这么想  还是我们完蛋了
Is it just me, or are we completely screwed?
快点  理查德  快接电话
Oh, come on, Richard. Pick up.
还没消息吗
Still no word?
好几个小时没消息了
No, not for hours.
很漂亮  不是吗
It's beautiful, isn't it?
简直完美
It's perfect.
真不敢相信阿丽克西斯和玛莎能布置好这里
I can't believe Alexis and Martha pulled this off.
现在就缺新郎和新娘了
Now all we need is a bride and groom.
离婚礼开始只有不到24小时了
The wedding's less than 24 hours away.
希望他们能赶到
I hope they make it.
告诉我这也是童话的一部分吧
Tell me this is - still part of the fairy tale.
如果是  那也是格林暗黑童话
If it is, it's a Grimm one.
你们觉得他们会怎么做
What do you -- what do you think they're gonna do?
我觉得
My guess --
一旦他们拿回照片  他们就会杀了我们
once they recover the photos, they'll probably kill us.
是啊  成就史上最糟单身派对
Yes, making this - the worst bachelor party ever!
别看我啊
Don't look at me.
要不是她那么固执不肯给我松绑
Okay, we would've been out of there
我们早就逃出去了
if she hadn't gotten all stubborn and just cut me loose.
你大可以签了文件  让我解脱啊
You could've just signed those papers and cut me loose.
不管你信不信
Hey, believe it or not,
我只是想补偿蒂尔迪
I was just trying to do the right thing for Tildy.
靠敲诈一位牧师吗
By blackmailing a pastor?
拜托  别被那牧师骗了
Oh, please. Don't let the collar fool you.
他活该
That guy had it coming.
不会吧  你说牧师活该
Really?! The pastor had it coming?
没错  他告诉我了一个投资机会
Yes. He told me about this investment opportunity
可以让我的钱翻一番
where I could double my money.
只是  我没钱  所以我问蒂尔迪借了
Only...I didn't have any money, so I borrowed tildy's.
猜猜发生了什么  那就是个骗局
Well, guess what. It was a scam.
那人骗我好付钱给那个脱衣舞女
The guy was rooking me to pay off the stripper.
这破了多少戒律啊
I mean, how many broken commandments is that?
所以我就自己扛下来了
So I took matters into my own hands, you know?
那可真他妈的是个好计划
And it was a -- it was a damn fine plan, too.
除了...
Except the...
出来个杀人黑手党的部分
murderous mobster part.
我真没想到会变成这样
I really didn't see that coming.
我们还没完
This isn't over.
我们能逃出去  肯定有办法的
We're gonna get out of this. There's a way.
洗耳恭听
Love to hear it.
这贼有个老婆
So, the thief has a wife.
很好
That's good.
这下好办多了
That makes this all a lot easier.
照片在哪里
Where are those photos?
我说过了  我不知道你在说什么
I-I-I told you -- I don't know what you're talking about.
你猜怎么着
Well, guess what.
我来刺激你一下
I can incentivize you.
照片在哪里
Where are the photos?
听我说  我...
Okay, look, I...
我删除了  没有了
I-I deleted them. They're gone.
我发誓
I swear.
我才不相信你
I don't believe you.
我数到三
I'm gonna count to three.
你要是还不告诉我照片在哪
You don't tell me where they are,
那你也用不着这些法律文件了
You're not gonna need these court papers.
我亲手了结你的婚姻
I'll end your marriage for you.
一
One...
二
Two...
我知道  我...
I know. I...
我知道照片在哪
I know where they are.
我...
I...
我知道照片在哪
I know where they are.
在他家  有台笔记本电脑
They're on a laptop -- at his place.
我和她能帮你拿过来
She and I can take you to them.
没错
Yeah.
那好吧
All right.
我们一起去吧
Why don't we all go?
为什么他要带上所有人
So, why are they taking all of us?
你说呢
Why do you think?
丈夫  妻子  未婚夫  你的公寓
Husband, wife, future husband, your apartment.
当他们找到我们的尸体
When they find our dead bodies,
嫉妒泄愤这种故事说都不用说
the story of jealous rage writes itself.
把门打开
Open the door.
米奇  相信我  你不想这么做
Mickey, trust me -- - you don't want to do this.
相信我  我想
Trust me -- I do.
好了  笔记本电脑在哪里
Okay. Where's the laptop?
不
No.
我的钱呢
Where's my money?
这怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
你要钱  钱就在那
You want your money? It's right there.
这是米奇·巴保兹  联调局的通缉犯
This is Mickey Barbozza. He's wanted by the FBI.
然后呢
So?
抓到他有赏金
So, there's a reward for his capture --
十万美金
$100,000.
你抓到他  钱就是你的
You take him in, it's all yours.
走吧  硬汉
Let's go, tough guy.
你俩真是太厉害了
That was a hell of an angle you guys played.
我想  我应该感谢你俩
I guess, uh, - I should be thanking you both
救了我的命
for... saving my ass.
那些流氓摩托车手的贡献也不小
Don't forget the contribution of the homicidal bikers.
那你现在可以
Yeah, so, um, maybe you could sign...
签字了吧
the papers now.
当然
Oh, yeah. Okay.
好的
Okay.
听我说  小凯
You know, Kit Kat...
别为我们的离婚难过好吗
I don't want you to be sad about this, okay?
没有我你会过的更好
'cause you're better off without me.
你就签吧
Just sign the papers.
好的
Okay.
好啦
There you go!
你很幸运  家伙事
You are a lucky man, man parts.
我
I, uh...
真希望也拥有你们那样的爱情
I just wish I had what you guys have.
也许你已经有了
Well, maybe you already do.
你说蒂尔迪吗
With Tildy?
不好说
Uh...I don't know, man.
我完全搞砸了
I... I screwed that up.
经历了这么多
You know, I mean, a-after all this,
我也没把她的钱弄回来
I didn't even get her money back,
她就要被我害的失去酒吧了
and she's gonna lose the bar because of me.
不一定
Not necessarily.
这是鲍伯牧师给的
From pastor Bob.
什么
What?
两万五千块作为骗你钱的补偿
A $25,000 apology for scamming that money from you.
他说只要以后不用再见到你和那些照片
He says if he never sees you or those photos again,
你俩就算扯平
you're even.
罗根  搞什么啊
Rogan, what the hell?
我说了我不想再在这见到你
I told you I never wanted to see you in here again!
蒂尔迪  蒂尔迪  等等
Tildy, Tildy, wait. Just...
我有个坏消息告诉你
I got some bad news.
我昏迷的妻子她
My wife that was in a coma...
去世了
she died.
天哪
Oh, my god.
-是啊  -太遗憾了
- Yeah. - Oh, I'm so sorry.
别  这样对她更好
Don't be. She's in a much better place.
她留给我了一些钱
She she left me some money,
我想  想给你
and I -- I just... I want to give it to you.
我
I...
我爱你  蒂尔迪
I love you, Tildy.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我们走
Come with me.
不敢相信你居然把鲍伯牧师的钱给他了
I can't believe you gave him the money from pastor Bob.
我喜欢幸福的结局
I'm a sucker for happy endings.
赶紧离开这  我们的幸福还等着呢
Let's get the hell out of this town and go get our own.
好棒
Yes!
我们要结婚了
We're getting married!
客人都到了  你准备好了吗
People are starting to arrive. Are you ready?
快好了
Almost.
你怎么做到的
How did you pull this off?
我给你爸打了个电话
Oh, you know, I called your dad.
他说有你能穿的婚纱
He said he had a dress you could wear.
你美得像个天使
You look like an angel.
真的吗
Really?
是啊  我都想娶你了
Yeah. For a second there, I wanted to marry you.
别闹啦  蕾妮
Oh, just stop, Lanie.
我得说  你母亲眼光独到
I must say, - your mother had great taste.
确实
Yes, she did.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
你是我见过的
I believe you are - the most beautiful bride
最美的新娘
I have ever seen.
谢谢你  玛莎
Thank you, Martha.
蕾妮  亲爱的  能让我们单独聊聊吗
Lanie, darling, could you just give us a minute?
好的  我去告诉你父亲婚纱很合身
Sure. I'll just tell your dad that it's perfect!
谢谢  蕾妮
Thanks, Lanie.
玛莎  我真的好感激
Martha, - I-I just wanted to tell you
你和阿丽克西斯
how grateful I am to you and alexis for --
为我们做的这一切
for putting all of this together.
我要感谢你让我儿子如此幸福
And I want to thank you - for making my son so very happy.
我给你准备了一样东西
I brought you something --
以备你没有蓝色的东西
in case you didn't have something blue.
天哪
Oh, wow.
太美了
They're... beautiful.
这是我妈妈送给我
They were given to me by my mother
在婚礼上戴的
to wear on my wedding day,
而且是她妈妈当年送给她的
and by her mother before.
只有有内涵的女人才戴过哦
Only women of substance have worn these gems.
它们一直在等你  凯瑟琳
They've been waiting, Katherine, for you.
我太荣幸了  玛莎
I'm so honored, Martha.
谢谢你
Thank you.
亲爱的  你戴着美极了
Oh, darling, they're exquisite on you.
抱歉
Oh, excuse me.
是他的电话
It's him.
那我就不打扰你和新郎聊天啦
Oh. Well, I will leave you to talk to your groom.
我先出去了
I'll be outside.
亲爱的  你快到了吗
Hey, lover. How close are you?
再20分钟吧
20 minutes.
告诉你个好消息  法官那边办得很顺利
And you'll be happy to know things went smoothly with the judge.
你自由啦
You are a free woman.
不过也自由不了多久
But not for long.
我们的结婚证就装在我口袋里
I got our marriage license in my pocket.
我马上就到
I will be there soon.
还有  凯特
And, Kate...
什么
Yeah?
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
都一个小时了
It's been an hour already,
大家都有点着急了
and the natives down there are getting restless.
你说他去哪了
Where do you think he is?
不知道
I don't know.
我最后一次和他通话
When I spoke to him last,
他说20分钟就到
he said he was - less than 20 minutes away.
我是理查德·卡塞尔  请留言
This is Richard Castle. Leave me a message.
直接转接语音信箱了
Straight to voicemail.
喂
Hello?
我就是
Yes. This is she.